H. Alexander Smith Papers, 1897-1966 (bulk 1920-1966 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 4: Senatorial Career, 1931-1958; 159.67 linear feet 376 boxes
  - Subseries 4E: Public Issues, 1944-1958; 59.21 linear feet 142 boxes
    - 1947, portions of 2 boxes
      - Austin, Warren R, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Brown, Philip Marshall, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Cabot Lodge, Senator Henry, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Correspondence A-L, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Correspondence M-R, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Correspondence R-Z, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - European Trip, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Farm Journal, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Gates, Moore, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Labor, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Linton, M. Albert, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - McGraw Hill Publishing Company, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Nowinson, Richard, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Paul, Winston, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Peaslee, Amos, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Princeton University, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - United News, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Vanderbilt, Arthur T, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - 1948, 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - 80th Congress, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Alaska Veterans Project, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Altschul, Frank, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Atkins, Dr. Paul, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Bosshart, Rev. John, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Bowlby, Henry L, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Brakeley, George, Princeton University, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Coffee With Congress, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Contributions, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Correspondence A-D, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Correspondence D-K, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Correspondence K-P, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Correspondence R-S, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Correspondence T-Z, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Delaware River, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Driscoll, Governor Alfred E, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Election Results, Primary, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Hendrickson, Robert C, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Knowlton, Daniel, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Kerney, James, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - MacArt, James A., 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Mallery, Otto, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Merck, George, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - McGraw Hill Publishing, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - New Jersey Republican Finance Committee, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Photographs, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Questionnaires, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Republican National Committee, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Rutgers University, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Republican National Committee, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Republican Party Policy, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Smith, H. Alexander, Office, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Sokolsy’s Articles, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Stewart, Johnston F, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Van Nest, John S, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Vanderbilt, Arthur, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Votes, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Voice of America, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 19)
    - 1947-1950, 4 boxes (1 partial)
      - Acheson, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Aid to China, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Atomic Energy Contract, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Austin, Warren R, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Bilbo, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Bretton Woods, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Budget, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Civil Junction Bill, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Clippings, 1948-1950; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Community Credit, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Conscientious Objectors, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Cooperatives, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - District of Columbia Hospital Bill, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Driscoll, Governor Alfred, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - European Recovery Program, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Equal Rights, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Fair Employment Practices Committee, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Federal State Taxes, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Greece, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Hendrickson, Senator Robert C, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Housing, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Hoover Dam, 1947-1950; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Income Tax Bill, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Inflation, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Institute for Advanced Study, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Income Tax, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Labor, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Labor Courts, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Lilienthal Appointment, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous Releases, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - National Survivor Foundation, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Postwar Economic Policy and Planning, 1946; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Presidential Campaign, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Presidential Successor, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Rent Control, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Republican Steering Committee, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Railroad Reorganization Act, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Republican Majority Conferences, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Republican National Convention, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Smith, H. Alexander, Illness, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Special Session 80th Congress, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Spain, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Italian Peace Treaty, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Tourism in European Proper, 1948-1950; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Town Hall Correspondence, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Town Hall Miscellaneous, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Tideland Bill, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Trivanovitch, Vaso, 1949; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Truman, President, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Unification of Armed Forces, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - United Nations Charter, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Universal Military Training, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Watson, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Wheat Agreement, 1948; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - World Disarmament, 1947; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - 1951, 3 boxes (2 partial)
      - Appropriations, Agriculture, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Budget, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Clippings, Foreign, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Clippings, Domestic, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Committee Assignments, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Court of Military Appeals, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Defense Agency, Acquisition and Disposal of Property, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Defense, Housing, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Defense, Interstate Compact, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Defense Production Act, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Dispersal and Decentralization of Federal Agencies, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Dispersal of Federal Agencies, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Distributions of Judgeships, Third Circuit, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - District of Columbia Home Rule, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Drafting 18 Year-Old Boys, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Economy, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Fake Vacancy, Hartshorne, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Federal Judiciary, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Hartshorne, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Judgeship Tax Court, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Modarelli Confirmation, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Partisanship in Judiciary, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Resolution, Partisanship in Judiciary and Speech, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Special Committee to Investigate Organized Crime in Interstate Commerce, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on Public Affairs and State Department Organization, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - S. 349 Defense Housing, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - 1952, 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Editorials, Special, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Clippings, Domestic, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Clippings, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Clippings, Foreign, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Armed Services Pay Bill, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Atomic Energy Commission, Pike Appointment, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Budgetary and Fiscal Policy, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Carlsen, Kurt, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Claremont Terminal, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Congressional Executive Relations, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Cloture, General, 1951; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Electoral College, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Elizabeth-Newark Airport, Plane Crashes, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Elizabeth-Newark Airport, Clippings, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Emergency Powers, Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Federal Survey Management, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Investigative Procedure, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Small Business Committee, Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Tidelands, Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Submerged Lands, Tidelands, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - President Truman, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Public Utilities, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Universal Military Training and Service, Foreign Relations Committee and ROTC, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Universal Military Training, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Women’s Suffrage, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - 1952-1957, 4 boxes (1 partial)
      - A, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, General, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Deficiency Appropriation Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Air Mail Subsidy, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - B, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Bills to be Introduced, Requests for Smith to Sponsor, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Budget, General, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Budget Speech, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - C, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Civil Rights, H. R. 6127, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Civil Rights, Segregation, Cloture-Senate Rule 22, Releases, Statements, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Civil Rights Commission, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - "The People Take The Lead," Booklets, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Annual Report, "Ten Year of Progress in Civil Rights," Booklet, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Segregation Speech, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Civil Rights Subcommittee, Fair Employment Practices Committee, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Civil Rights, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Walter White, Fair Employment Practices Committee, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Civil Rights, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Campaign, Negro, Fair Employment Practices Committee, New Jersey, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Robeson Newspaper Clippings, Walter White, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Segregation, Southern Senators, Marshall, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Civil Rights, Miscellaneous Material, 1947-1952; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Cloture, Senate Rules Number 22, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - D, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - E, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - President Eisenhower, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - President Eisenhower, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - President Eisenhower, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Elections, 1952; 1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - President Eisenhower, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - President Eisenhower, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Elections, President and Vice-President, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Elections, Corrupt Practices, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Electoral College, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Electoral College, 1953-1956; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - F, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Federal National Mortgage Association-Home Loan, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Federal Land Ownership, Long, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Financial Condition, U.S., Investigation, Finance Committee, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Financial Institution Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Fiscal Policy and Inflation, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - G, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - General Services Administration, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - H, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Hells Canyon Dam, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Hermann, Albert B, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - I, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Investigations, Campaign Expenditures and Lobbying, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Investigations, Rules of Procedures for Senate Committee; T.V. and Broadcasts; Committee, Personnel, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - J, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - K, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - L, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - League of Women Voters of New Jersey, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Louisiana Oil Rights, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - M, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Modern Republicans, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - N, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Narcotics, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Negotiated Conflicts, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Niagara Falls, Development Hydroelectric Power, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Vice President Nixon, 1954-1951; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - O, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - P, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Poultry, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Post Office Rates, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - President’s Council on Youth Fitness, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Presidential Vetoes, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Public Buildings Act of 1949 Senator Francis Case, 1957, 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Presidential Papers, Microfilming, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Preferential Primary Elections, 1953-1955; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Q, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Questionnaires, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Pierson, Drew, 1950; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - R, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - S, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Sick Leave, Act of, 1951; 1953; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Ship Owners’ Liability, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Small Business Administration, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Social Security, Delaware River Port Authority, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - T, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Excise Tax, Fulbright, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - U, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - V, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Veterans’ Housing in Rural Areas and Small Cities, Thurmond’s Amendments, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - W, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - X, Y, Z, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Wherry, Elizabeth, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - White House, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 29)
    - 1953, 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Agriculture, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Air Mail Subsidy Separation, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Anti-Trust Act Revision, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Appropriation Bill, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Appropriation Bill, State Justice and Commerce, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Appropriations, Byrd Expenditure Control Resolution, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Bush, Vannevar, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Civil Defense, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Consumer Interests, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Controls, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Governorship, Primary, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Hoover, Reorganization, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Rent Control, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Tidelands, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Treasury Department, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Truman, President, State of the Union Address, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Waterfront Compact, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - White House Meetings, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - A-Z, Around the World Trip, 1953; 2 boxes (1 partial)
        - General, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 12)
        - Burma, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
        - Formosa, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 2)
        - France, Paris, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 3)
        - Hong Kong, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 4)
        - Indo-China, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 5)
        - India, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 6)
        - Lebanon, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 7)
        - Japan, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 8)
        - Korea, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 9)
        - Thailand, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous, 1953; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - 1954, 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Batsto, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Becker, George H, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - Botany Mills, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Bristol-Myers, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Clark, W. M, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Correspondence A-J, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Correspondence M-Z, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Dominick, Peter, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Driscoll, Governor, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Employment Security, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Hendrickson, Dan, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Lincoln Day Dinner, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - McCloy, John, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - New Jersey Campaign Contributions, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - New Jersey Republican Party, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - New Jersey Senatorial Campaign, Case Candidacy, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - New Jersey Senatorial Campaign, Constituent Letters, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - New Jersey Senatorial Campaign, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - New Jersey Senatorial Campaign, Newspaper Clippings, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - New Jersey Senatorial Primary, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - New Jersey State Committee Dinner, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      - New York Ship Building Corporation, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      - Republican National Committee, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Republican Party, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Taft, Robert A, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Tuck, Hallam, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - United Nations, Fall Session, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Unusual Letters, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - 1954-1958, 2 boxes (1 partial)
      - Hoover Commission, Miscellaneous, 1954-1958; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Hoover Commission Recommendations, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Hoover Commission Federal Medical Services, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Hoover Commission Bills, Clippings, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - General Correspondence, Hoover, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Work on Reports, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Hoover Commission, General, 1955; 2 folders (Folder 2 to 3)
      - Federal Advisory Council of Health, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      - Hoover, Accrued Expenditures, Appropriations, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - Administrative Court, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Civil Service, Personnel Administration, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Federal Civil Service Act, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - Improving Management and Technical Personnel, Department of Defense, 1957; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - Reorganization Record, Hoover, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - Hoover Bills to be Introduced, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Statement on Introduction of Hoover Bills, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch, 1954; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Administrative Vice President, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 14)
      - Budget and Accounting, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 15)
      - Budget and Accounting, Government Operations, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      - Business Enterprises, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 17)
      - Business Enterprises, Post Office and Civil Service Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 18)
      - Business Enterprises, Public Works Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 19)
      - Business Organization of the Department of Defense, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 20)
      - Depot Utilization, Armed Forces Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      - Depot Utilization, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 22)
      - Federal Medical Services, Labor and Public Welfare Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 23)
      - Food and Clothing, Armed Services Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      - Intelligence Activities, Foreign Relations Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 25)
      - Legal Services, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 26)
      - Legal Services, Judiciary Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 27)
      - Legal Services, Armed Services Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 28)
      - Lending Agencies, Banking and Currency Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 29)
      - Lending Agencies, Agriculture and Forestry Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 30)
      - Lending Agencies, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 31)
      - Lending Agencies, Finance Committee, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 32)
      - Overseas Economic Operations, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 33)
      - Paperwork Management, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 34)
      - Personnel and Civil Service, Post Office and Civil Service Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 35)
      - Personnel and Civil Service, Finance, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 36)
      - Personnel and Civil Service, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 37)
      - Personnel and Civil Service, Judiciary, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 38)
      - Real Property Management, Armed Services Committee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 39)
      - Real Property Management, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 40)
      - Research and Development, Labor and Public Welfare Committee, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 41)
      - Surplus Property, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 42)
      - Transportation, Kennedy’s Subcommittee, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 43)
      - Water Resource and Power, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 44)
      - Disposal of Excess and Surplus Property, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 45)
      - Improve Legal Procedures in Executive Branch by Enactment of Administrative Code, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Folder 46)
      - Proposed Joint Committee on Central Intelligence, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Folder 47)
      - Parcel Post and Indirect Costs, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 48)
      - Periodical Inspection of Loans Prohibited, 1955-1956; 1 folder (Folder 49)
      - Payment of Claims Against the Government, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 50)
      - Transfer Fertilizer Research Facilities to Department of Agriculture, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 51)
      - Transfer Functions of Post Office Department to Federal Prison Industries, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 52)
      - Comptroller Organization of Department of Defense Supervision, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 53)
      - Credit Policy, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 54)
      - Lending Agencies and Annual Reports, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 55)
      - Bureau of the Budget Comprehensive Reports Bill, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 56)
      - National Industrial Reserve, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 57)
      - Federal Crop Insurance Corporation Premiums, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 58)
      - Export, Import Bank, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 59)
    - 1955, 3 boxes (1 partial)
      - Air Force Academy, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      - Columbia University, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 2)